varagesale.com 2018-12-26

# VarageSale - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At VarageSale we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, to protect our rights or as otherwise disclosed in here.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.
  * Your trust is the most important thing to us. We will never do anything evil with your information that could break this trust.

Below is our Privacy Policy which incorporates these goals and promises.

If you have questions about this policy, please contact our support team at [help@varagesale.com](mailto:help@varagesale.com).

VerticalScope Inc. operates the website located at www.varagesale.com (“Website” or “VarageSale”) as well as mobile applications available on application stores including the Apple App Store, Google Play Store and Amazon Kindle App Store (each, an “App”). It is VarageSale’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our service. This Privacy Policy applies to visitors of our Website as well as users who register for an account through the Website and/or App.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, VarageSale collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. VarageSale’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how VarageSale’s visitors use its service. From time to time, VarageSale may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, for example, by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its service.

To ensure the safety of our users, VarageSale also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users participating in VarageSale communities.

### Social Log-in

You have the option to register for an account using your account credentials with third-party social platform providers such as Facebook. If you register using your third-party account credentials, we will also collect and use the personal information associated with your third-party account according to this Privacy Policy. The information we will have access to in respect of your third-party account will depend on the applicable third-party platform provider’s privacy policy as well as any applicable privacy preferences you may have selected in respect of your third-party account.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to VarageSale’s service choose to interact with VarageSale in ways that require VarageSale to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that VarageSale gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for VarageSale to provide an email address. In each case, VarageSale collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with VarageSale. VarageSale does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Aggregated Statistics

VarageSale may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its service. For instance, VarageSale may monitor the most popular items. VarageSale may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, VarageSale does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

VarageSale discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on VarageSale’s behalf or to provide services available through the Website and/or App, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. VarageSale will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, VarageSale discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when VarageSale believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of VarageSale, third parties or the public at large. Our service providers may host data in the United States, and accordingly your personal information may be made available to government agencies in the United States if our service providers receive a government request for access.

VarageSale takes commercially reasonable measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Communications

If you are a registered user of VarageSale and have supplied your email address, VarageSale may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with VarageSale and our products. If you are located in a jurisdiction that requires opt-in consent for such communications, we will only send you such messages if you opt-in to receive them. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum, and you may unsubscribe at any time.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. VarageSale uses cookies to help VarageSale identify visitors, monitor their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. For example, cookies allow you to log in to VarageSale. VarageSale visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, VarageSale may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in VarageSale’s sole discretion. VarageSale encourages visitors to periodically check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

VarageSale is located at [111 Peter St, Suite 901, Toronto, ON, M5V 2H1](https://www.google.ca/maps/place/111+Peter+St,+Toronto,+ON+M5V+2G9/@43.647862,-79.3929029,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x882b34da8a94a0f5:0xf64a5b658d21638e).

_Last Updated: May 22, 2018_
